Privacy Policy - The Children's Guild                                                            

Select Page

Privacy Policy
==============

1. [Home](https://childrensguild.org/)
2. Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

The Children’s Guild Alliance operates this website. Our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use states our policies pertaining to the collection, use, and disclosure of data that contains personal information of anyone accessing this website provided by The Children’s Guild Alliance. By using our website, you agree to the collection and use of information detailed in this policy. Any information that we collect is used for improving this website. We do not use and/or share your information with anyone except as described.

##### Information Collection and Use

While using this website, we may ask you to provide us with personal information such as your name and contact information. The data that we collect will be used to contact or identify you. We may also collect and store other information about your online activities but we do not obtain any personal information about you in this instance. The information collected is used to operate and enhance our site. If you share a comment or a suggestion, we ask that you provide your contact and other pertinent information. In some cases, we may use your personal information to provide information back to you. The Children’s Guild Alliance will not sell your personal information. The Children’s Guild Alliance may share information, including your comments, with third parties to further the mission and purposes of The Children’s Guild Alliance. However, you can request that your information and/or comments be kept confidential.

##### Log Data

By visiting this website, we collect log data, information that your browser sends to us. Log data information may include your device’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser, type of device used, pages accessed on this website, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, country of access, and other relevant information.

##### Cookies

We use cookies to collect information and to enhance our web service and you have the option to accept or refuse the collection of cookies. If you choose to refuse cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our website..

##### Third-Party Providers

We utilize third-party companies and/or individuals plus partners and school systems due to the following reasons:

* To facilitate our web services
* To provide the web services on our behalf
* To perform web-related services
* To assist us in analyzing how our web service is used
* To complete forms, applications, and payment processing

These third parties may have access to your personal information you provide to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, third parties are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose. Third parties partners include, but not limited to:

##### Security

We strive to use the best methods to protect your personal information. No method of transmission over the Internet or digital storage is 100 percent secure and reliable. We do not guarantee the absolute security of your personal data and information.

##### Links to Other Websites

This website may contain links to other sites, these websites are not owned or operated by us and we advise you to review the privacy policy of these other sites.

##### Protecting Children’s Privacy

We do not knowingly collect information from children that are under the age of 13. If we discover that a child has provided us with personal information, we take immediate action to delete it from our servers. If you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please [\[email protected\]](https://childrensguild.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) so that we can take the necessary actions.

Terms of Use
============

When visiting our website, we assume you accept these terms and conditions. Do not continue to use The Children’s Guild Alliance website if you do not agree to the terms and conditions.

##### Frames and Appearances

Without prior approval and written permission, you may not create frames around our web pages that alter in any way the appearance of our website on another website or matterial.

##### Content Liability

We are not responsible for any content that appears on your website. You agree to protect and defend us against all claims that arise on your website. No link(s) should appear on any website that may be interpreted as libelous, obscene or criminal, or which infringes, otherwise violates, or advocates the infringement or other violation of, any third party rights.

##### Reservation of Rights

We reserve the right to amend our terms and conditions and request that you remove links to our website at any time. By linking to our website, you agree to immediately remove links upon request and to follow these terms and conditions.

##### Removal of Links from our Website

If you find a link on our website that is offensive, please contact us and we will consider your request. We are not obligated to remove links nor to respond to you directly. We do not ensure that the information on this website is correct, we do not warrant its completeness or accuracy; nor do we promise to ensure that the website remains available or that the material on the website is current.

##### Disclaimer

To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, we exclude all representations, warranties, and conditions relating to our website and the use of this website. Nothing in this disclaimer will:

* Limit or exclude our or your liability for death or personal injury
* Limit or exclude our or your liability for fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation
* Limit any of our or your liabilities in any way that is not permitted under applicable law
* Exclude any of our or your liabilities that may not be excluded under applicable law

The limitations and prohibitions of liability set in this section and elsewhere in this disclaimer: (a) are subject to the preceding paragraph; and (b) govern all liabilities arising under the disclaimer, including liabilities arising in contract, in tort and for breach of statutory duty.

As long as the website and the information and services on the website are provided free of charge, we will not be liable for any loss or damage of any nature.

##### Updates to the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use

Periodically, we may update our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use and advise you to review this page periodically for any changes. Updates made to the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use are effective immediately after they are posted to this page.

**Headquarters**  
1200 First St NE 2nd Floor  
Washington, DC 20002  
[\[email protected\]](https://childrensguild.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**Administrative Offices**  
6802 McClean Blvd.  
Baltimore, MD 21234-7260  
[\[email protected\]](https://childrensguild.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  

#### [Schools & Career Services:](https://childrensguild.org/schools-career/)

#### [Child, Family, & Community Programs:](https://childrensguild.org/child-family-community/)

#### [Community Care:](https://childrensguild.org/community-care/)

#### **Follow Us:**

The Children’s Guild and its affiliates maintain policies to promote equal opportunity and to protect against discrimination and harassment, in accordance with applicable law.

© 2024 The Children’s Guild. All Rights Reserved
